Say your prayers.
Longlegs is a crime, horror, mystery film directed by Osgood Perkins.
FBI Agent Lee Harker is a gifted new recruit assigned to the
unsolved case of an elusive serial killer.
As the case takes complex turns, unearthing evidence of the occult, Harker discovers a personal connection to the
merciless killer and must race against time to stop him before he claims the lives of another innocent family.
Agent Lee Harker, played by Maika Monroe.
Longlegs, played by Nicolas Cage.
Agent Carter, played by Blair Underwood.
Ruth Harker, played by Alicia Witt.
Agent Browning, played by Michelle Choi-Lee.
Agent Fisk, played by Dakota Daulby.
Longlegs is a 2024 American mystery horror thriller film
written and directed by Osgood Perkins.
The film stars Maika Monroe, Blair Underwood, Alicia Witt, and Nicolas Cage.
Set in the 1990s, the story follows a Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) agent assigned to hunt down an
occult-obsessed serial killer responsible for a string of family murders across Oregon.
The killer is dubbed Longlegs, and baffles the FBI with his perfect ability to
seemingly leave zero trace of involvement at the crime scenes.
Cage served as a producer on the film through his
Saturn Films production company.
Longlegs premiered in Los Angeles at the Grauman's Egyptian Theatre on July 8, 2024, and
was released theatrically in the United States by Neon on July 12, 2024.
It received positive reviews and grossed $128 million worldwide on a budget of less than $10 million, becoming Neon's
highest-grossing film domestically, the highest-grossing independent film of the year, and Perkins's highest-grossing film.
The film explores themes of homicide, fbi, religion
and supernatural, haunting, satanism.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and thought_provoking.